<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Video App</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="About"><u>About App</u></string>
    <string name="link">Follow and connect me on my social profiles and do visit
        my website .\n\n
    Website: <a href="https://get2logics.com/">https://get2logics.com/</a>\n
        and subscribe to my youtube channel .\n\n
        Channel :<a href="https://www.youtube.com/@priyankanigam6239/playlists">Get2logics</a></string>
    <string name="about">
        This is Video Player app which is android friendly.It is both an offline as well as online based app.
All the videos that i have added here are actually my own self made apps which are currently live
streamed on my youtube channel - Get2logics.\n
I have integrated AI eye detecting feature in this app.  So videos can be watched in normal mode and AI
mode both. In normal mode  the video will be streamed online through youtube google server.
When you switch to AI mode  the videos will be available offline there and will be played from
your app memory.The main functonality of this mode is that if your eyes are off  than no video will be
played.The video will get pause if you close your eyes.The video will play only if your eyes are open or else
it will be in pause state.\n\n

I have added share functionality in the app.You can share the app link which is actually a youtube link to
a 3rd person or app. I have also given the app source code link within the app to clone the app code into
your machine and have also given the APK file to view the actual app and also the complete file in the compressed
zip format to download.On Long pressing any app list item or a popup will open asking you to
share the app to others or download the APK file of the app or the PDF or view the source code of that linked app.\n

Here are some other features in the app too. Like to enable dark mode view for your app or optimize the screen
brightness from within the app.And also a picture-in-picture mode or so that you do not have to exit from the
app while running some other app.This feature is very helpful for the device which do not support split screen
mode.With this you can simultaneously work on multiple apps without exiting from this app.\n
This app will be very helpful in the low internet speed or bandwidth hotspot.You can play your video without
any buffering or pre-loading issue.\n

The videos will play in HD quality by-default but you can customise your video quality to different supportable
pixel size in the normal video mode.Some good facts about this app is are :\n
Stability.
Robust reporting and analytics.
Lightweight.
Curations own playlists.
Direct management.
Seamless integrations.
You will not face any sound or picture quality issue in the app.If you feel that our app is lacking any good feature
or is laden with bugs or incomplete functionality .Feel free to connect us .\n

You can connect with me through my website : www.get2logics.com\n
I also have a youtube channel as - Get2logics .\n Please watch my videos and do like and subscribe to my channel.
You can also comment me there  i will try to give my response as soon
as possible.




    </string>
</resources>